My name is Jake I grew up in the Appalachian Mountains and I know all of the rules.
And I broke one of them a month ago ever since I keep feeling watched.
I'm 24 years old and a month ago I was drinking while on call with my best friend and he was also.
Drinking. His mother recently died of a heart attack he was feeling down.
It was about one in the morning I locked all my doors and closed my blinds.
He was talking about maybe coming over.
I wish I said no but I was drunk and not in the right state of mind.
He hangs up and I wait.
Around 15 minutes later I hear a knock.
I forgot to text him and confirm.
I go to open the door and see nothing.
I yell out his name.
You there? Nothing but the wind howling.
The forest was awfully quiet.
I shut the door and go back inside.
Minutes go by and I get a weird gut feeling.
It was all a haze was at 30 or 15 minutes I was drunk out of my mind I'm surprised I.
Remembered what happened.
For what seems like forever my phone chimes.
Jasper.
Yo almost there be there in 10 minutes.
I look at the text and feel my heart drop.
What the fuck did I just do?
I nearly had a panic attack.
I heard Jasper's voice calling out from outside it sounded like a faint call in the wind.
I begin to hear taps on the windows all around.
I really don't know what it is but I've been hearing whispers in the other room and footsteps
and.
Knox.
For my friend I called him told him to go back home and we will remain on call for the rest
of the night.
I explained the whole situation to him.